hi everyone and welcome to yoga with
Adrien I'm Adrien and today we're going
to continue our foundations of yoga
series by learning Warrior 2 another
standing posture so hop on the mat and
let's learn Vasa
[Music]
2 okay so I'm going to begin in a nice
wide lay
position a nice wide angle my feet are
going to be wider than my hips but I
don't need to go super wide here I want
to feel nice and stable cing my hands to
my hips here just take a deep breath in
and then exhale take a look sees down at
your feet I'm going to turn my left toes
in and my right toes out towards the
front edge of the mat or the back Edge
The Edge so I have my right toes
pointing straight forward now my left
toes are pointing in towards the left
corner of my mat or maybe towards the
left corner of the room I'm going to
bring my attention to the outer edge of
that back leg nice and strong right so
pressing into my base here finding my
Universal alignment as I kind of scoop
that tailbone in draw my navl in and
lift and lengthen up through the spine
so I'm not rushing anything here I'm
kind of coming into the body integrating
everything together before I enter into
my posture now I'll inhale spread the
fingertips wide right fingertips go
front left fingertips go back and as I
exhale keep keeping this lengthen my
spine the heart lifted I'm going to sink
into my posture so I inhale lift and
lengthen and exhale with the arms nice
and wide fingertips wide
I bend my front knee and check out
Warrior 2 today couple of action points
couple of alignment notes I don't want
this knee to go past my ankle in fact I
want it to be the shin to be
perpendicular to the Earth and kind of
create a nice right angle here so I can
walk my toes out if I need a little more
space or I can walk them in if I need to
find more stability but I want to get to
a place where I can see my front big toe
so if the knee is coming in which is
going to be a tendency I'm going to say
no thank you mindful bring it out and
see if I can take a look down at my big
toe now my right arm is extending out
excuse me my left arm is is extending
out nice and long my right arm is going
towards the front of the room and then I
Just Breathe Here check in maintaining
the Integrity of that back
foot maintaining the length in my spine
as I get tired this leg is going to want
to unbend but I'm going to sink in deep
breathing into my full
torso as I'm here I can take a check
into the shoulders by inhaling opening
The Palms wide ah open
heart and then keeping this spiral in
the shoulders and this open heart I'm
going to Pancake The Palms back down but
keep the shoulders where they
are can maybe try that again in inhaling
opening the
shoulders and then turning the Palms
over so I'm maintaining this nice open
spiral of the shoulders rather than
being
here that's an exaggeration of course
but I'm creating a little space growing
from there and then Palms back down
parallel to the
Earth again no breath count again today
we're just breathing here I just want to
encourage you to Breathe Here drawing up
through the arches of the feet pressing
into that outer edge of the back leg
Warrior the Mantra or the affirmation
here is I am
strong that's we do in kids yoga I am
strong like
Warrior nice and easy in the face strong
in the lower body keep tucking that
pelvis in and then when you feel
satisfied here we'll inhale in exhale
straighten that front leg release the
hands to the waistline turn both big
toes in and take it to the other side
side turning the left toes
out right toes in again coming into mind
alignment inhale reaching the fingertips
front to back and
exhaling into my posture now I don't
just hang out here I go through the same
action
points and
breathe okay so that was Warrior 2 give
it a try let me know if you have any
questions or comments leave them in the
comment box below um if you haven't
already please subscribe to the channel
and uh I'm going to be doing a Q&A I've
been getting some questions which is
great because that's why we do this to
start a conversation a dialogue to help
you out I'm here to serve you help you
grow a yoga practice so um let me know
what you're thinking leave your
questions and we'll do a special Q&A
video coming up soon and we'll keep
doing them if uh we keep getting the
questions so thank you and have a
beautiful day
namaste
[Music]